{
    "id": "72df58a28e4749c196d1a71183ad021d",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The car suffered heavy damage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "car",
                "heavy",
                "damage"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Every dog has his day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "dog",
                "day"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have bought enough sugar.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "enough",
                "sugar"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was wearing a blue gown.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wearing",
                "blue",
                "gown"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have had my fair share of disappointments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "fair",
                "disappointments"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The way was long and the wind was cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "way",
                "long",
                "wind"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Donâ€™t cry over spilt milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cry",
                "over",
                "spilt"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He won the first prize.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "first",
                "prize"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a man of few words.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "man",
                "of",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He died a glorious death.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "glorious",
                "death"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A small leak can sink a great ship.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leak",
                "sink",
                "great"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "King Francis was a hearty king and loved a royal sport.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hearty",
                "and",
                "sport"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}